The Israeli government have brazenly, publicly and openly declared their intention to commit
a war crime and have commenced that war crime against the people of Gaza, saying that they
intend to starve of food, electricity, water, 2.2 million people.
They are raining down thousands of the most sophisticated missiles known to humanity onto
the most densely populated area in the world, carrying the certainty that almost every missile
will incur civilian casualties.
And you try to suggest there is some symmetry, some equivalence between the actions of Hamas
and what Israel has been doing to the Palestinians for decades.
Is this getting clearer for y'all yet?
Are you there yet?
Are you starting to understand?